<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio&#39;s Rodolfo Valentim</title>
    <link>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio&#39;s Rodolfo Valentim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 14:10:31 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 14:10:31 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>RDNA Balance: Load Balancing by Isolation of Elephant Flows using Strict Source Routing (2019). Rodolfo V. Valentim, Cristina. K. Dominicini, Diego R. Mafioletti1, Rodolfo S. Villaca, Moises R. N. Ribeiro, Magnos Martinello - LANCOMM Student Workshop (Latin American Student Workshop on Data Communication Networks), 2019, Gramado - RS
 RDNA Balance: Balanceamento de Carga por Isolamento de Fluxos Elefante em Data Centers com Roteamento na Origem (2019). Rodolfo V. Valentim, Cristina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Render LaTeX using KaTeX</title>
      <link>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/posts/render-latex-using-katex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/posts/render-latex-using-katex/</guid>
      <description>Enable katex by adding katex = &amp;quot;true&amp;quot; to the front matter
+++ katex = &amp;#34;true&amp;#34; +++ It&amp;rsquo;s almost a dropin alternative to the mathjax solution,you should just choose one of them.
Inline math looks like this
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} =1$ This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$
and with math blocks:
$$\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} =1$$ $$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Rodolfo</title>
      <link>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Education  M.Sc. in Computer Sciente - Computer Networks Federal University of Espírito Santo - Vitória, ES, Brazil 2018 - Present
 Graduated in Computer Engineering Federal University of Espírito Santo - Vitória, ES, Brazil 2012 - 2017
  Professional and Academic Experience  Researcher/MSc. student at the UFES Software Defined Networks Research Group NERDS, UFES - Vitória, ES, Brazil 2017 - Present
 Research project relate to Load Balancing in Cloud Environment  Research project relate to Service Function Chaining in Cloud Environment  Research project on Network Functions Virtualization using OpenStack   Researcher/B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me, @Rodolfo77835271.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rodolfovalentim.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects  Playground - Interactive Technology Playground is a tool for building applications that use interactive totems to amplify event results. Our applications are flexible and allow our clients to transform real goals (in participation in branded exhibition events) into playful and fun dynamics to attract the target audience and achieve maximum results
 vCPE - Network equipment virtualization Development of a vCPE (Virtual Customer Premises Equipment) prototype using the OpenStack platform as a cloud resource manager.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>